<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on Legogoa Axi0m</title><link>https://legogoa-axiom.github.io/pages/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on Legogoa Axi0m</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://legogoa-axiom.github.io/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Credits</title><link>https://legogoa-axiom.github.io/credits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://legogoa-axiom.github.io/credits/</guid><description>We are very thankful for the people who help us so this is our way of saying thankyou to them 1) Dr. Pramod Maurya, Scientist NIO 2) Mr. Amey Karmali, CIBA - Center For Incubation And Business Acceleration 3) Ryan Vaz, Infinity 3D Systems 4) Amey Borkar, Infinty 3D Systems</description></item><item><title>FTC</title><link>https://legogoa-axiom.github.io/FTC/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://legogoa-axiom.github.io/FTC/</guid><description>What is FTC? •FIRST Tech Challenge is the ultimate Sport for the Mind.
•High-school student participants .
•Under strict rules, limited time and resources, teams of students are challenged to raise funds, design a team &amp;ldquo;brand,&amp;rdquo; hone teamwork skills, and build and program industrial-size robots to play a difficult field game against like-minded competitors.
•It’s as close to real-world engineering as a student can get.
•Volunteer professional mentors lend their time and talents to guide each team.</description></item><item><title>Our team</title><link>https://legogoa-axiom.github.io/team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://legogoa-axiom.github.io/team/</guid><description>👨🏽‍💻Team Members These are all the people in our team.
👨‍💻 Vighnesh Nauso Shetye I am a student studying in class 9th. I like to learn and explore various aspects of technology including coding, robotics, the internet and so on.
My Achievements: 2nd rank at Jigyasa international problem solving fair competition 1st place in state-level Codeavour 2021 3rd place in national level Tcs rural quiz. 1st place in smart school hackathon 2nd place in the Indian technology and Science festival.</description></item><item><title>Sponsor us</title><link>https://legogoa-axiom.github.io/sponsor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://legogoa-axiom.github.io/sponsor/</guid><description>Participating in a competition of this scale needs considerable funds and resources and we would be grateful to receive help from you in any possible way. •There are a number of ways that you can help us. We would be deeply thankful to receive:
•Funding for our project (however much you can donate).
•Parts or tools to help us make our robot
•Giving us access to your social media following or connections to allow us to spread the word about our group</description></item></channel></rss>